

CURRICULUM VITAE

My name is Mattia Marsetti and I was born in the Alps in 1992. After playing with the famous bricks for almost a decade I dedicated my teens in mastering Latin and Greek, while self-teaching informatics. Then I found my way into Engineering, while spending my summers in volunteering. I'm currently working on the Powertrain SW that runs the Ferrari GT and Motorsport cars.



WORK EXPERIENCES

MOTORSPORT SW SPECIALIST – Competizioni GT
SW Development, Integration and Testing for GT3 and LMH projects
Ferrari - Maranello

POWERTRAIN CONTROL ENGINEER – GT Cars
Set up of the SW Sharing environment with the Supplier and SW
Development from Requirements to Tests
Ferrari - Maranello

2017-2020

2020 - now



EDUCATION

MASTER DEGREE - Automation and Control Engineering	2011-2016
Politecnico di Milano - Milano	

HIGH SCHOOL – Diploma di maturità Classica 2006-2011 Liceo G. Piazzi - Sondrio



OTHER EXPERIENCES

VOLUNTEER	2014-2017
Phone operator & visits to the hospital for CasAmica - Milano	

REFUGEE EMERGENCY OPERATOR logistics, transportations for CARITAS – Palermo Integration project for a refugee family – Sondrio

EDUCATOR
Kids education for Centro di Apojo Infanto Juvanil – Corumbà (Brazil)

LUG-AUG
2013



SKILLS

- SW DEV. & DATA ANALYSIS: mainly Matlab/Simulink, often EXCEL, always GIT
- PLAN & PROCESS DEV: Agile Development in JIRA and SW Life-Cyle Development with Polarion
- CALIBRATION/DEBUG: proficient with CRETA INCA RACECON MDA ECU Diagnostics

CONTACTS

(+39) 349 167 2584

marsigliomarsetti@gmail.com

Via Caggiati 2, Reggio Emilia (IT)

ON THE WEB

in Linkedin

NO Twitter/Facebook/Instagram

LANGUAGES

ITALIAN

- native

ENGLISH

- fluent

INTERESTS

Books and Comics
Board games
Analogue Photography
Snowboard

PRIVACY

In compliance with the GDPR and the Italian Legislative Decree no. 196 dated 30/06/2003, I hereby authorize you to use and process my personal details contained in this document

Version: 1.28 - 16/03/21
Check out on GitHub